intelihealth.com 2013-12-22

# Aetna InteliHealth's Privacy Policy - Intelihealth

|  | 

Aetna InteliHealth's Privacy Policy

Aetna InteliHealth has been a leader in setting ethical standards for Internet consumer health websites. We may periodically revise the privacy policy. When we make significant changes that affect our collection and use of your personal information or our security practices, we will post a notice on the Aetna InteliHealth home page for 30 days. We recommend that you read our privacy policy whenever you visit our site in case you missed our notice or have not registered for a service or feature of our site previously.

When you visit and navigate our website, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. By "personal information," we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, e-mail address or telephone number.

You are always welcome to use the Aetna InteliHealth site without registering or providing any personal information. However, we require you to register for certain services, including our free health e-mails and other features, including "Send this page to a friend." When you use these features, we will clearly disclose what information is required, what information is optional and how that information may be used.

When you click on "Send this page to a friend" at the bottom of any of our pages, we will ask for your e-mail address and the address of the person receiving the page. We will not disclose to third parties any identifying personal information gathered from you during registration for e-mails and other features unless (1) we tell you how your information will be used and you give Aetna InteliHealth specific permission to share this information or (2) Aetna InteliHealth is required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process (like a subpoena or court order). Where we disclose identifying personal information to third parties with your authorization, we will require the recipient to use the information only for the purpose provided.

Access to the data within Aetna InteliHealth is limited to a few computer technicians for our site who need to maintain the database and who also use passwords for that access, as well as outside vendors who may occasionally assist us in maintaining and improving our hardware and software tools.

We make every effort to safeguard your personal information. However, like other websites, we cannot guarantee that it is completely secure from people who might attempt to evade security measures or intercept transmissions over the Internet.

Similarly, we cannot completely ensure the privacy of e-mail communications to and from our site because they are not encrypted and, therefore, not secure. These communications, like most Internet e-mail, could be intercepted without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to or from our site. This includes e-mail you send to us through our various mailboxes, our free e-mails for specific health topics and information e-mailed from our site to others using features such as "Send this page to a friend." If you are concerned about your privacy, we suggest that you do not use e-mail to communicate information to us that you consider sensitive.

When you register for Aetna InteliHealth's free health e-mails, your information is not secure during transmission to us.

When you use our "Send this page to a friend," the information you submit is stored by us for 30 days to allow your friend or relative to "pick up" the information you sent. The information is stored behind an electronic firewall.

You can change the personal information in your Aetna InteliHealth profile at any time by clicking on "Change Profile" on the navigation bar at the bottom of any page on our site. Or you can visit Change Profile. If you forget your password, visit the change profile page and we will e-mail your password to you. As with most e-mails, this transmission is not secure.

Unsubscribing from our free health e-mails does not delete your personal information from our system, even if you unsubscribe from all e-mails. We will delete your personal registration information from the active and searchable areas of our system at your request. Be aware, however, that it is not feasible for us to remove every electronic record that may contain your data. We cannot remove copies of your information that may exist in records we create as backup in case our main data is lost. We also cannot delete information from anonymous, aggregated databases. This information cannot be linked to you. We maintain and archive all personally-identifiable information provided by users. This data is retained in our archives and not deleted.

To have your registration information removed, send your request by e-mail to [ihonline@aetna.com](mailto:ihonline@aetna.com). You will receive a confirmation from us.

If you have any concerns about the security or privacy of your personal identifiable information on the Aetna InteliHealth website, please contact us at [ihonline@aetna.com](mailto:ihonline@aetna.com) or send a written notification to:

> Aetna InteliHealth  
> 980 Jolly Road  
> Blue Bell, PA 19422  
> Attn: Customer Servcie

When you sign up for free health e-mails, we maintain information about your selections only for the purpose of sending you the e-mails. We do not use identifying personal information for any other purpose although it may be included in anonymous, aggregated statistical information.

We will send you only information that you request.

Instructions for unsubscribing from e-mails are located at the bottom of each e-mail. Click the link given and uncheck each subscription you wish to cancel. You also can unsubscribe by using the "Change Profile" link at the bottom of any page on our site. Unsubscribing from e-mails does not delete your personal information from our system, even if you unsubscribe from all e-mails.

Aetna InteliHealth no longer hosts discussion boards.

Cookies are small bits of information placed on your computer's hard drive by a website. It is a simple text file that helps your browser remember certain information that the website can later retrieve to streamline communication between your browser and the website. Aetna InteliHealth does not store this information. Our site can only read the cookies placed on your computer by us. We cannot access any information on your hard drive placed there by you or any other source.

The Aetna InteliHealth website uses only benign cookies that have no functionality. This means the cookie cannot do anything to your computer's hard drive and cannot read information from your computer's hard drive.

The Aetna InteliHealth website uses cookies for user convenience. The cookie will tell our system certain information so you don't have to fill in the same information each time you visit us. An example of this is our "Send this page to a friend" feature.

We also may use cookies on an aggregate basis to track site navigation. This information is not traceable to an individual user. Navigation streams are used to assist us in determining where people go when visiting our site and how long they stay in a particular area. This information is used to improve our site and may be shared with advertisers.

Unlike many other websites, the Aetna InteliHealth website does not use cookies to tailor information that appears during your visit to your preferences or your use of our site.

If you click on a sponsorship acknowledgment, you will be leaving Aetna InteliHealth and will be directed to the sponsor's site. Be aware that we have no control over the practices of other websites. Your computer may receive cookies from other sites and you will not be protected by Aetna InteliHealth's security and privacy policies.

The cookie feature can be turned off on your browser. For more information on turning off the cookie feature, consult your browser help section. If you choose to turn off cookies, you can still access all areas of our site. Once the cookie feature on your browser is turned off, you might have to "refuse" a cookie each time you encounter one searching our site.

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP) whenever you access the Internet. This number may be the same each time you access the Internet or it may change. Like other Internet sites, Aetna InteliHealth uses IP addresses to collect aggregate information about numbers of visitors and site usage. The address is logged on the server that services this site when your computer requests information from Aetna InteliHealth. However, to allow users to access our site anonymously, your IP address is not linked with personal information about you. Aetna InteliHealth and Healthline Networks reserve the right, in rare instances, to use IP addresses to identify individuals who threaten the site, service or customers.

When you respond to surveys, questionnaires or polls on our site, we may, at times, ask you for demographic information such as your gender or age. This information is collected only as anonymous, aggregated information and is used for statistical purposes. Otherwise, we do not collect or store your personal responses.

When we run a contest, we may ask for personal information when you enter the contest. If so, we will describe in each instance why we are asking for that personal information and how we plan to use that information.

We will not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to register on our site for any purpose or to access any features that require registration. We require visitors to indicate their year of birth to register. If we learn that we inadvertently have collected identifying personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete that information from our system.

We do not collect information about searches that you perform on our site.

This privacy policy applies only as long as you remain on the Aetna InteliHealth website. Once you leave Aetna InteliHealth to visit another site, we have no control over your privacy or security issues even if you reached the other site by clicking on a link within Aetna InteliHealth.

Throughout Aetna InteliHealth, you will see links that can lead you to another site. If you click on an advertisement or sponsorship acknowledgment while you are on Aetna InteliHealth, you will be leaving Aetna InteliHealth and will be directed to the advertiser or sponsor's site. Also, if you click on a link or a "Return to" or "Back to" banner for another website, you will be leaving Aetna InteliHealth and will be directed to the linked website. Aetna InteliHealth also offers listings of resources that contain links to the websites of government agencies and non-profit organizations. If you click on those links, you will be leaving Aetna InteliHealth and will be taken to the website of that agency or organization. At times, clicking on a hyperlink within an article will bring up information on another site without warning. In these cases, however, the information will appear in a second, smaller "pop-up" window and the Aetna InteliHealth page will remain clearly visible on your computer screen.

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

This policy was effective on September 28, 1998

Last updated September 04, 2012  
  
---|---
